Gabrielle Giffords Papers, 1995-2012 (bulk 2007-2012)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup I: Congressional Activities, 1995-2012
  - Series 1: Committee Files, 1995-2012
    - Subseries 2: Foreign Affairs, 2007-2010
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, United States-Mexico Security Cooperation, May 24, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, Violent Crime Analysis, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, United States Policy in the Middle East, October 24, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Subseries 3: Science and Technology, 1995-2012
      This subseries contains materials related to Giffords’ work on the Science and Technology committee such as legislation and issues related to the committee.
      - Department of Energy's Energy Research and Development Program, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - General Hearing Information, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Plans and Procedures, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Algae biofuel, January 5, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Amendment to the Export Enhancement Act of 1988, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Amendment to Internal Revenue Code of 1986, April 27, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, American Power Act, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, American Recovery and Reinvestment Act, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Arizona Solar Energy, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Arizona Water (1 of 6), 2008-2010 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Arizona Water (2 of 6), 2008-2010 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Arizona Water (3 of 6), 2008-2010 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Arizona Water (4 of 6), 2008-2010 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Arizona Water (5 of 6), 2008-2010 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Arizona Water (6 of 6), 2008-2010 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, British Petroleum Oil Spill, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Bureau of Land Management, Arizona Public Service Right-of-Way application, 2002-2009 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Carbon Sequestration, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Clean Energy, 2008-2010 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Climate Change, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Committee Activities, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Conservation, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Dark Sky Association, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Deep Water Drilling Hearing, June 23, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Department of Energy proposed budget, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Electric cars, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Energy Bill provisions, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, energy efficiency (1 of 3), 2007-2009 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, energy efficiency (2 of 3), 2007-2009 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, energy efficiency (3 of 3), 2007-2009 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, energy storage, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Federal Lands, 2005-2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general energy (1 of 3), 2007 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general energy (2 of 3), 2007 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general energy (3 of 3), 2007 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general energy (1 of 2), 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general energy (2 of 2), 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general solar (1 of 6), 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general solar (2 of 6), 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general solar (3 of 6), 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general solar (4 of 6), 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general solar (5 of 6), 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, general solar (6 of 6), 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, geoengineering, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, geothermal comments, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, geothermal energy (1 of 3), 2006-2008 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, geothermal energy (2 of 3), 2006-2008 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, geothermal energy (3 of 3), 2006-2008 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Global Climate Response Act, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Hearing on Utility Scale Solar Power, March 17, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Hoover Dam Power legislation, January 6, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 39- Udall-Eisenhower Arctic Wilderness Act, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 1698- Green Bank Act, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 2304- Advanced Geothermal Energy Research and Development Act, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 2313- Marine Renewable Energy Research and Development Act, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 2484- Harmful Algal Blooms and Hypoxia Research and Control Amendments Act, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 3585- Solar Technology Roadmap Act (1 of 4), 2010 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 3585- Solar Technology Roadmap Act (2 of 4), 2010 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 3585- Solar Technology Roadmap Act (3 of 4), 2010 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 3585- Solar Technology Roadmap Act (4 of 4), 2010 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 4959- Global Conservation Act, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, H.R. 6160- Rare Earths and Critical Materials Revitalization Act, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Hydropower, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, land and development (1 of 2), 2008-2010 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, land and development (2 of 2), 2008-2010 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, National Association of Counties 2008 Legislative Conference (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, National Science Foundation Authorization Act, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, National Science Foundation budget requests, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, natural gas, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, North Central Arizona water supply study, October, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, nuclear energy, 2007-2011 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Nuclear Energy Research and Development Act, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, ocean energy, 2005-2007 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, oil and coal, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Oil Pollution Research and Development Program Reauthorization Act, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, renewable energy, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Renewable Fuel Standard report, January 23, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Scialog materials, October, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, science parks, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Solar Agency contracts, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Solar Field Hearing, March 17, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Solar Grand Plan, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Solar ITC advocacy, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, solar land issues, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, solar legislation, June 22, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, solar legislation, October 7, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Solar Next Steps, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, solar reports (1 of 2), 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, solar reports (2 of 2), 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, solar roadmap markup, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Solar Technology Roadmap Act, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, solar/water use, 2007-2009 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Southwest Energy Innovation Forum, October 18, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Sunzia Southwest Transmission Project, 2009-2011 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Tohono O'Odham Nation Sif Oidak water claims, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, transmission legislation, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Tucson Water water plan, February 5, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, wind energy, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on Energy and Environment, Water Resources Development Act, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee General, 111th Congress Member briefing book, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Subcommittee General, 112th Congress Member briefing book, 2011-2012 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee General, Climate Change, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee General, Finances, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee General, General Science, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee General, General Science, 2007-2011 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee General, H.R. 2036- Marine and Hydrokinetic Renewable Energy Promotion Act, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee General, H.R. 2096- Cybersecurity Enhancement Act, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee General, H.R. 2304- Advanced Geothermal Energy Research and Development Act, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, America COMPETES, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, America COMPETES Act (1 of 3), 2009-2011 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, America COMPETES Act (2 of 3), 2009-2011 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, America COMPETES Act (3 of 3), 2009-2011 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, Elementary and Second Education Act, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, Energy Policy Act of 2005, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, General, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, General RSE, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, H.R. 2313- Marine Renewable Energy Research and Development Act, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, H.R. 2454- American Clean Energy and Security Act, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, H.R. 6899- Comprehensive American Energy Security and Consumer Protection Act, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, Impact Aid for Rural Schools, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, K-12 STEM Education, 2009-2010 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on Research and Science Education, Workforce Development for Teachers and Scientists, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, 111th Congress (1 of 2), 2007-2009 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, 111th Congress (2 of 2), 2007-2009 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Act to Authorize National Aeronautics and Space Administration programs for Fiscal Year 2011-2013 (S. 379) (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Advanced Research Projects Agency, January 27, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Air Force, March, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Augustine letters sent from Committee, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Cost Effective Return to the Moon by D.L. Jensen, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Enhancing the Relevance of Space to Address National Needs, July, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Fairness and Contracting Integrity in the National Aeronautics and Space Administration's Space Communications Networks Services Competition, July 13, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, General National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 2009-2011 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers Federal Sector issues, April, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, James D. Webb Telescope, April, 2011-December, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Markup notebook for Authorization Act, July 22, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Statement, National Aeronautics and Space Administration's Administrator Charles F. Bolden, February 25, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Annual Report on enhanced leasing, May, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration Authorization Act of 2008 logistics contingency plan for International Space Station, March, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration Authorization Act of 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration Authorization Act of 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration Authorization Act of 2010 Amendment in the Nature of a Substitute (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration budget (1 of 2), 2011 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration budget (2 of 2), 2011 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Constellation Program, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Fiscal Year 2012 Operating Plan Submission, January 10, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Glenn Research Center, December 7, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Human Space Flight Capability Assurance and Enhancement Act, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Human Space Flight Hearing, September 15, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Human Space Flight Hearing, December 2, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Human Space Flight Hearing, May 26, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Hearing on Proposed Changes to Exploration Program, March 24, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, International Collaboration in Human Space Flight beyond Low-Earth Orbit report, March, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Presentations, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Presidential budget request, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Report on Education Implementation Outcomes, March 8, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Report Regarding Transitioning Experimental Research to Operations, March, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Report on Suborbital Research Activities, January, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, STS 128 Mission Summary, August, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Science Foundation and the National Institute of Standards and Technology Budget (1 of 2), 2011 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Science Foundation and the National Institute of Standards and Technology Budget (2 of 2), 2011 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, National Space Foundation, July 26, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Possible Questions for Chairwoman Giffords Hearing on Mitigating the Impact of Volcanic Ash, May 5, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Review of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration's Acquisition of Commercial Launch Services, February 17, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Shuttle Derived Heavy-Lift Launch Vehicle Assessment (1 of 2), June 8, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Shuttle Derived Heavy-Lift Launch Vehicle Assessment (2 of 2), June 8, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Space Exploration Alliance, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Space Hearings, June, 2009-May, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Space Policy Recommendation of Houston chapter of National Society of Black Engineers Alumni Extension, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Space Summit, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics, Space X, March 5, 2010-March 7, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Technology, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Subcommittee on Space and Technology, National Aeronautics and Space Administration and the Notification and Federal Employee Antidiscrimination and Retaliation Act of 2002, March, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Subcommittee on Technology and Innovation, H.R. 1425- Creating Jobs Through Small Business Innovation Act, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Subcommittee on Technology and Innovation, H.R. 2463- Border Security Technology Innovation Act, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Subcommittee on Technology and Innovation, International Space Station's Contribution to Natural Competitiveness Enhancement Report, 2010-2011 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Subcommittee on Technology and Innovation, Manufacturing, 2007-2010 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Subcommittee on Technology and Innovation, Research Parks and Job Creation, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Series 2: Legislative Activity Files, 2007-2012
    This series contains materials related to Giffords’ congressional activities including appropriations requests, the Blue Dog Coalition, bill cosponsor solicitations, floor statements, legislative work primarily on the border, immigration, healthcare and energy, district related legislation and some research for legislative work. It is arranged alphabetically.
    - American Health Care Association-National Center for Assisted Living Congressional Briefing, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - America's Affordable Health Choices Act, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - American Cancer Society Cancer Action Network, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Plan presentations, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (1 of 2), 2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (2 of 2), 2009 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act PowerPoint presentations and notes, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations Committee- Defense Requests (1 of 3), 2007-2012 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations Committee- Defense Requests (2 of 3), 2007-2012 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations Committee- Defense Requests (3 of 3), 2007-2012 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2008 requests (1 of 6), 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2008 requests (2 of 6), 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2008 requests (3 of 6), 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2008 requests (4 of 6), 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2008 requests (5 of 6), 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2008 requests (6 of 6), 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2009 Defense appropriations requests, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2009 requests (1 of 2), 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)